[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Okay people, listen up.
Today, we're talking about fermions.
Fermions have a half-integer spin
NOT a full-integer spin;
those are bosons.
Where am I?
Uh, hold on.
I think we're going to have to
move to another room.
Somebody's renovating this place, I guess.
I'm so confused.
My head hurts.
Man, I'm sore all over.
Feel like I got my ass kicked.
Jesus Christ.
What was I doing in there?
How did I even get in here?
I want a drink.
It doesn't have to be bourbon;
I'm not too picky.
You know, anything at least 80-proof.
It smells like dog vomit in here.
Oh, a hatch.  There's the answer.
Ohh, I don't know if I can reach it.
I'll find a stick or something.
What the hell did I do last night?
I remember there was
some guy with an eye patch.
And a midget.
Oh, perfect.
What were they talking about?
[growls]
And some sort of scam
involving corndogs.
Shit, I don't remember.
Ergh, can't reach.
I can tell already this is
going to be a fun day.
Rah!
Come on!
This sucks.
[yawns]
Seriously, how did I get here?
I can't go through my
whole life living like this.
Oh, drain.
If I party this hard every night, I'm
going to end up dead in a few years.
I don't remember what happened.
I think I was watching
a movie about monsters...
...and they attacked Canada?
I mean, obviously, SOMETHING happened.
I woke up in a trash compactor again.
Yeah, this looks easier.
Hey, the ruptured rusty rods reveal a rift!
Whoa, wait, which way is up?
Oh. Okay, that's cool.
See?  An exit.
I'm one of the kids who paid attention
to the hamsters in class.
[coughs]
Wow, this is not my finest hour, is it?
Spending the night in the Dumpster,
getting dumped out of a sewer pipe
facedown into a run-off puddle,
waking up in the afternoon,
I'm probably missing work,
I'm lost in the desert,
I have many unexplained bruises
and facial lacerations...
They say you know when
you hit rock bottom,
but I can't say any of this
is completely unfamiliar.
Except for being in the desert.
That's kind of new.
The last time something like
this happened was Austria.
Actually, Austria was even worse
because I woke up naked.
I had to wander around lost in Innsbruck
until I could make some clothes
out of old garbage bags.
[teleportation sound]
Okay, well, this part's different.
Is this the only road?
Eh...  God, that's a big cockroach.
[headcrab squeals]
Jesus!
That's the size of a friggin' softball.
On second thought, I don't
think that is a cockroach.
Looks like something
out of South America.
I should start watching
National Geographic again.
Oh, there's another one.
I don't like the desert.
Shit...
[coughing]
Someday, I'll be president
and it'll put this all in perspective.
Oh! Shit!
Somebody had a worse night than me.
I'm not touching anything; I'm not going
to be part of the crime scene.
That is rule number one
to staying out of prison.
And to making proper measurements
on quantum particles.
Man, I want to get back to the lab.
No, wait, something happened
to it, didn't it?
Huh.  A giant bung.
I'm not seeing an entrance.
Good God, I'm in the middle of nowhere.
How did I get here? Am I a werewolf?
Eh, butts.
I'll go this way.
Christ, it's hot out here.
I caught a break being
passed out in the shade.
Otherwise, my face would be sunburned.
It's always real classy going to parties
with half of your face burned red.
This isn't the right way.
I should come down.
Uh...
Oh, that'll work.
Okay...
Not bad.
I could've gotten some
sick air if I had a pogo stick.
And a jet pack.
And... all right, I need to get out of here.
Wandering lost in the desert
is not good for my career.
Hey, what's this do?
Oh, wow, it spins by itself.
That...that's lazy.
Power steering for when you're
too tired to turn a valve.
What's our obesity rate at?
Isn't it like 30%?
This is why I'm not in administration.
I would've taken the
money for powered valves
and used it to put a door
on the side of the building.
Oh, hey, there's something down here.
Lights and...
oh, there's the door!
Okay. I was confused.
I have silly ideas about building design.
Like, I wouldn't make people climb--
Oh, hell. Maybe that's how that guy died.
I should be careful...
Yeah, maybe he was just stepping
outside the building for a smoke break,
climbed the ladder up the silo,
slipped at the top,
then splat!
I could be a detective.
Although, as I say that, I still haven't
figured out what happened last night.
I remember having problems.
Lots of problems.
I'm pretty sure about that.
Ah, it's an elevator.
Like something we might've
built in the Middle Ages.
If we had motors...
and water.
All right, well, I think this was meant
to be operated by a second person,
but if I double-time it, I should
be able to get up there.
I wonder why it was designed this way.
It was probably because of a union
contract that says that we have to hire
so many elevator workers
and this is to accommodate that.
Da, dada, dada!
Climb, climb, climb!
Monkey madness!
Gotta get up to get down!
Whoo...
Hurgh...
Huh... well...
I'm pretty sure that this
isn't the executive elevator.
That would have carpeting.
Oh.
This is kind of a crappy entrance, huh?
Oh well. I didn't see any rose petals
waiting for me on the outside.
Still, with our budget,
this kind of bullshit.
I think there's some class warfare
going on at this company.
[gunshots]
Whoa.
What's going on in here?
I've gotta check this out.
I seem to remember
a lot of gunfire from yesterday.
That's odd.
Oh, he dropped his clip.
I'll take it. Maybe I can
sell it back to him.
I wonder how much I can get from him.
Probably at least 20 bucks.
[guard groans]
[squish]
Ugh! What's going on here?
FUCK!
Okay, something's not right here.
This requires further investigation.
[squish]
I'm not going to get
my 20 bucks from him, am I?
[splat]